(Howard:)So this spring, I get to go
to the International Space Station.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, my word, a trip to the heavens.
If you ever wanna live there eternally,
I've got a good book you could read.
(Howard:)I watch the Charlie Brown
Christmas Special every year...
(Howard:)...so I get the gist.
(Mrs Cooper:)I bet your mom is really proud of you.
(Howard:)Nope. She says if I don't back out,
she's gonna go on a hunger strike.
Um, it would take years before she'd be
in any kind of danger, but still.
(Sheldon:)I've got a treat for us tomorrow, Mom.
(Sheldon:)I'm taking you to see
Saul Perlmutter give a lecture...
(Sheldon:)...about his Nobel Prize-winning
work in cosmology.
(Sheldon:)And the best part is,
at the Q and A afterward...
(Sheldon:)...I've worked up a couple of
Q's that will stump his sorry A.
(Mrs Cooper:)I don't know, Shelly. I thought we could
do a little sightseeing.
(Sheldon:)What sight is better than your little boy
embarrassing a Nobel Iaureate?